Federal Music Project Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Programs, 1935-1943 (Box 36-137)
  - 1938 (Box 67-91)
    - Rhode Island, (13 folders) (Box 90)
    - South Carolina, (2 folders) (Box 90)
    - Tennessee, (3 folders) (Box 90)
    - Texas, (7 folders) (Box 90)
    - Texas (cont.), (7 folders) (Box 91)
    - Utah, (2 folders) (Box 91)
    - Vermont, (2 folders) (Box 91)
    - Virginia, (2 folders) (Box 91)
    - West Virginia, (3 folders) (Box 91)
    - Wisconsin, (2 folders) (Box 91)
  - 1939 (Box 92-111)
    - California, (35 folders) (Box 92-95)
    - California (cont.), (4 folders) (Box 96)
    - Colorado, (2 folders) (Box 96)
    - Connecticut, (13 folders) (Box 96)
    - Delaware, (13 folders) (Box 97)
    - District of Columbia, (1 folder) (Box 97)
    - Florida, (3 folders) (Box 97)
    - Georgia, (2 folders) (Box 97)
    - Illinois, (7 folders) (Box 97)
    - Illinois (cont.), (6 folders) (Box 98)
    - Indiana, (2 folders) (Box 98)
    - Iowa, (3 folders) (Box 98)
    - Kansas, (2 folders) (Box 98)
    - Louisiana, (3 folders) (Box 98)
    - Maine, (3 folders) (Box 98)
    - Maryland, (3 folders) (Box 98)
    - Massachusetts, (4 folders) (Box 98)
    - Massachusetts (cont.), (9 folders) (Box 99)
    - Massachusetts (cont.), (2 folders) (Box 100)
    - Michigan, (8 folders) (Box 100)
    - Michigan (cont.), (6 folders) (Box 101)
    - Minnesota, (3 folders) (Box 101)
    - Mississippi, (3 folders) (Box 101)
    - Missouri, (9 folders) (Box 101)
    - Missouri (cont.), (5 folders) (Box 102)
    - Nebraska, (3 folders) (Box 102)
    - New Hampshire, (3 folders) (Box 102)
    - New Jersey, (3 folders) (Box 102)
    - New Mexico, (3 folders) (Box 102)
    - New York, (3 folders) (Box 102)
    - New York (cont.), (24 folders) (Box 103)
    - New York (cont.), (5 folders) (Box 104)
    - North Carolina, (3 folders) (Box 104)
    - Ohio, (2 folders) (Box 104)
    - Ohio (cont.), (19 folders) (Box 105-106)
    - Ohio (cont.), (6 folders) (Box 107)
    - Oklahoma, (3 folders) (Box 107)
    - Oregon, (3 folders) (Box 107)
    - Pennsylvania, (3 folders) (Box 107)
    - Pennsylvania (cont.), (16 folders) (Box 108-109)
    - Pennsylvania (cont.), (10 folders) (Box 110)
    - Rhode Island, (4 folders) (Box 110)
    - South Carolina, (2 folders) (Box 110)
    - Tennessee, (1 folder) (Box 110)
    - Texas, (4 folders) (Box 110)
    - Texas (cont.), (10 folders) (Box 111)
    - Utah, (2 folders) (Box 111)
    - Vermont, (2 folders) (Box 111)
    - Virginia, (1 folder) (Box 111)
    - Washington, (1 folder) (Box 111)
    - West Virginia, (3 folders) (Box 111)
    - Wisconsin, (3 folders) (Box 111)
  - 1940 (Box 112-127)
    - Arizona, (1 folder) (Box 112)
    - Arkansas, (2 folders) (Box 112)
    - California, (6 folders) (Box 112)
    - California (cont.), (6 folders) (Box 113)
    - California (cont.), (9 folders) (Box 114)
    - Colorado, (1 folder) (Box 114)
    - Connecticut, (5 folders) (Box 114)
    - Connecticut (cont.), (10 folders) (Box 115)
    - Delaware, (2 folders) (Box 115)
    - District of Columbia, (2 folders) (Box 115)
    - Florida, (2 folders) (Box 115)
    - Georgia, (1 folder) (Box 115)
    - Illinois, (4 folders) (Box 115)
    - Illinois (cont.), (7 folders) (Box 116)
    - Indiana, (2 folders) (Box 116)
    - Kansas, (2 folders) (Box 116)
    - Louisiana, (3 folders) (Box 116)
    - Maine, (1 folder) (Box 116)
    - Massachusetts, (6 folders) (Box 116)
    - Massachusetts (cont.), (5 folders) (Box 117)
    - Michigan, (8 folders) (Box 117)
    - Michigan (cont.), (4 folders) (Box 118)
    - Minnesota, (1 folder) (Box 118)
    - Missouri, (5 folders) (Box 118)
    - Missouri (cont.), (10 folders) (Box 119)
    - Nebraska, (1 folder) (Box 119)
    - New Hampshire, (1 folder) (Box 119)
    - New Jersey, (13 folders) (Box 120)
    - New Mexico, (1 folder) (Box 120)
    - New York, (25 folders) (Box 121)
    - North Carolina, (1 folder) (Box 121)
    - Ohio, (6 folders) (Box 122)
    - Ohio (cont.), (9 folders) (Box 123)
    - Oklahoma, (13 folders) (Box 124)
    - Oregon, (2 folders) (Box 124)
    - Pennsylvania, (7 folders) (Box 124)
    - Pennsylvania (cont.), (16 folders) (Box 125)
    - Rhode Island, (6 folders) (Box 125)
    - Rhode Island (cont.), (8 folders) (Box 126)
    - Texas, (8 folders) (Box 126)
    - Texas (cont.), (6 folders) (Box 127)
    - Utah, (1 folder) (Box 127)
    - West Virginia, (3 folders) (Box 127)
    - Wisconsin, (4 folders) (Box 127)
  - 1941 (Box 128-134)
    - Alabama, (1 folder) (Box 128)
    - Arkansas, (1 folder) (Box 128)
    - California, (13 folders) (Box 128)
    - Colorado, (2 folders) (Box 128)
    - Connecticut, (11 folders) (Box 128)
    - District of Columbia, (2 folders) (Box 129)
    - Delaware, (1 folder) (Box 129)
    - Georgia, (1 folder) (Box 129)
    - Illinois, (2 folders) (Box 129)
    - Iowa, (1 folder) (Box 129)
    - Kansas, (2 folders) (Box 129)
    - Louisiana, (1 folder) (Box 129)
    - Maine, (1 folder) (Box 129)
    - Maryland, (1 folder) (Box 129)
    - Massachusetts, (9 folders) (Box 129)
    - Massachusetts (cont.), (5 folders) (Box 130)
    - Michigan, (10 folders) (Box 130)
    - Minnesota, (2 folders) (Box 130)
    - Missouri, (12 folders) (Box 131)
    - Nebraska, (1 folder) (Box 131)
    - New Hampshire, (2 folders) (Box 131)
    - New Jersey, (5 folders) (Box 131)
    - New Jersey (cont.), (8 folders) (Box 132)
    - New York, (16 folders) (Box 132)
    - Ohio, (7 folders) (Box 132)
    - Ohio (cont.), (6 folders) (Box 133)
    - Oklahoma, (1 folder) (Box 133)
    - Oregon, (1 folder) (Box 133)
    - Pennsylvania, (10 folders) (Box 133)
    - Pennsylvania (cont.), (10 folders) (Box 134)
    - Rhode Island, (1 folder) (Box 134)
    - Texas, (8 folders) (Box 134)
    - Utah, (2 folders) (Box 134)
    - West Virginia, (1 folder) (Box 134)
    - Wisconsin, (2 folders) (Box 134)
  - 1942 (Box 135-137)
    - California, (1 folder) (Box 135)
    - Connecticut, (1 folder) (Box 135)
    - Illinois, (7 folders) (Box 135)
    - Iowa, (1 folder) (Box 135)
    - Kansas, (1 folder) (Box 135)
    - Massachusetts, (7 folders) (Box 135)
    - Minnesota, (1 folder) (Box 135)
    - Missouri, (4 folders) (Box 136)
    - New Hampshire, (1 folder) (Box 136)
    - New Jersey, (1 folder) (Box 136)
    - New York, (5 folders) (Box 136)
    - Ohio, (1 folder) (Box 136)
    - Oklahoma, (1 folder) (Box 136)
    - Pennsylvania, (8 folders) (Box 136)
    - Pennsylvania (cont.), (5 folders) (Box 137)
    - Rhode Island, (1 folder) (Box 137)
    - Tennessee, (1 folder) (Box 137)
    - Texas, (6 folders) (Box 137)
    - Utah, (1 folder) (Box 137)
    - West Virginia, (1 folder) (Box 137)
    - Wisconsin, (2 folders) (Box 137)
  - 1943 (Box 137)
    - Illinois, (1 folder) (Box 137)
- Clippings, 1935-1941 and undated (Box 138-142)
  Printed, typescript and photocopies of clippings from newspapers and magazines.
  Arranged chronologically by year, then alphabetically by state.
  - 1935-1939, (1 folder) (Box 138)
  - 1936-1940, n.d. (Box 138)
    - Scrapbook of Eva Arnow, Music analysis, (6 folders) (Box 138)
  - 1940 (Box 138-142)
    - Alabama, (1 folder) (Box 138)
    - Arizona, (1 folder) (Box 138)
    - Arkansas, (1 folder) (Box 138)
    - California, (3 folders) (Box 138)
    - California (cont.), (6 folders) (Box 139)
    - California (cont.), (1 folder) (Box 140)
    - Colorado, (1 folder) (Box 140)
    - Connecticut, (2 folders) (Box 140)
    - Delaware, (1 folder) (Box 140)
    - District of Columbia, (1 folder) (Box 140)
    - Florida, (1 folder) (Box 140)
    - Georgia, (1 folder) (Box 140)
    - Illinois, (1 folder) (Box 140)
    - Indiana, (1 folder) (Box 140)
    - Iowa, (1 folder) (Box 140)
    - Kansas, (1 folder) (Box 141)
    - Louisiana, (1 folder) (Box 141)
    - Maine, (1 folder) (Box 141)
    - Maryland, (1 folder) (Box 141)
    - Massachusetts, (1 folder) (Box 141)
    - Michigan, (2 folders) (Box 141)
    - Minnesota, (1 folder) (Box 141)
    - Mississippi, (1 folder) (Box 141)
    - Missouri, (1 folder) (Box 141)
    - Montana, (1 folder) (Box 141)
    - Nebraska, (1 folder) (Box 141)
    - Nevada, (1 folder) (Box 141)
    - New Hampshire, (1 folder) (Box 141)
    - New Jersey, (1 folder) (Box 141)
    - New Mexico, (1 folder) (Box 141)
    - New York, (1 folder) (Box 141)
    - North Carolina, (1 folder) (Box 141)
    - Ohio, (1 folder) (Box 141)
    - Oklahoma, (1 folder) (Box 141)
    - Oregon, (1 folder) (Box 142)
    - Pennsylvania, (1 folder) (Box 142)
    - Rhode Island, (1 folder) (Box 142)
    - Tennessee, (1 folder) (Box 142)
    - Texas, (1 folder) (Box 142)
    - Utah, (1 folder) (Box 142)
    - Virginia, (1 folder) (Box 142)
    - West Virginia, (1 folder) (Box 142)
    - Wisconsin, (1 folder) (Box 142)
  - 1941 (Box 142)
    - Connecticut, (1 folder) (Box 142)
    - Texas, (1 folder) (Box 142)
- George Allen Foster Collection, 1936-1948 and undated (Box 143)
  The papers of George Allen Foster consist of typescript correspondence, black and white photographs, printed and typescript programs and newspaper clippings, and reports.
  Each sub-series is arranged chronologically by year except for the photographs which are arranged alphabetically by name or subject.
  - Correspondence (Box 143)
    - 1936-1948, (1 folder) (Box 143)
  - Photographs, (1 folder) (Box 143)
    - Batjer, Margaret, c. 1940 (Box 143)
    - Childs, Sargent, n.d. (Box 143)
    - Christmas party, Roxbury, 1940 (Box 143)
    - Conference of music directors, P and S directors, 1941 (Box 143)
    - Cronin, Anne, n.d. (Box 143)
    - Foster, George, 1939 (Box 143)
    - Hopkins, Harry L., c. 1940 (Box 143)
    - Hopkins, Harry L. and E. Holger Cahill, c. 1940 (Box 143)
    - Miller, Izetta Jewel, n.d. (Box 143)
    - Morris, Lawrence S., n.d. (Box 143)
    - National Advisory Committee and State Music Project Supervisors Conference, New York, 1940 (Box 143)
    - Pelton, Paul, n.d. (Box 143)
    - Regional Conference of Federal Projects, Boston, 1938 (Box 143)
    - Reynolds, Senator (North Carolina), Boston, 1939 (Box 143)
    - Scott, Tula Martin, c. 1937 (Box 143)
    - "This work pays your community" or "See for yourself" broadcast, May 20-25, 1940 (Box 143)
    - WPA Tipica Orchestra, San Antonio, n.d. (Box 143)
    - Miscellaneous groups, c. 1939, n.d. (Box 143)
    - Miscellaneous groups, Des Moines, Iowa, c. 1939, n.d. (Box 143)
    - Unidentified, 1939 (Box 143)
  - Programs and Clippings (Box 143)
    - 1939-1940, n.d., (1 folder) (Box 143)
  - Reports (Box 143)
    - 1940-1944, (4 folders) (Box 143)